<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hengli Moments · Power Frontier on Hengli | Energy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hengli Moments · Power Frontier on Hengli | Energy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:07:10 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/english/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Customer Case: Solving the Efficiency Puzzle in the &#39;Last Three Kilometers&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;Hutong Express Supply Chain (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Industry:&lt;/strong&gt; Urban supply chain distribution, community retail/pharmaceutical instant delivery&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Application Scenario:&lt;/strong&gt; High-frequency, small-batch &amp;ldquo;last three kilometers&amp;rdquo; distribution in urban cores (using small electric trikes and micro-vans)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Cooperation Period:&lt;/strong&gt; June 2023 - Present&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Products Used:&lt;/strong&gt; Hengli New Energy High-Energy-Density, Long-Life LiFePO4 (LFP) Battery Packs&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Named Core Supplier for Industry Leader</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Through sustained dedication in the new energy power sector, we&amp;rsquo;ve achieved another major milestone: Secured a strategic order from Jiebu Power and officially become their core lithium battery supplier. This partnership demonstrates strong market recognition of our solutions and elevates our comprehensive competitiveness in power lithium batteries to new heights.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Launches Aggressive Overseas Market Strategy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After solidifying its leadership in China&amp;rsquo;s new energy power lithium battery market, the company has officially launched its overseas expansion strategy. Leveraging strong technical capabilities, exceptional product quality, and large-scale manufacturing advantages, we&amp;rsquo;re confidently bringing safe, efficient, and reliable lithium solutions to the global stage, actively participating in the worldwide green energy transition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough in Core Technology R&amp;D</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/english/blog/blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Amidst rapid battery technology evolution, our R&amp;amp;D center announces another exciting breakthrough. Leveraging strong independent R&amp;amp;D capabilities and forward-looking technology strategy, we&amp;rsquo;ve achieved significant advances in core material systems, battery structure design, and system integration. These innovations substantially enhance product performance and solidify our leadership in the power lithium battery sector. This milestone elevates our technological capabilities and powerfully supports the growing global demand for high-performance, safe, long-life lithium batteries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
